https://www.addstone.co.uk/privacy-policy.htm

Stick On, Plain
Stick On, Chamf.
String Course
More Stock...
String Course
...
See all Stock ...
Data Submission
From time to time on the Addstone™ website you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself (such as name, credit card/payment details, email address etc.) in order to receive or use services on the Addstone™ site. These services may include, but are not restricted to, online purchases, mailing lists and newsletters. Through input of your details in the page fields you enable Addstone™ and its service providers to provide you with the services you have selected. Whenever you submit this personal information Addstone™ will treat this information in accordance with the privacy policy detailed on this page.
Use and Storage of Personal Information
When you submit any personal information to Addstone™ we have legal obligations towards you in the way we use that data. This information must be collected fairly and, as detailed on this page, we are obliged to explain how we will use it. In general any information provided by you to Addstone™ will only be used by Addstone (UK) Limited (our trading company registered with Companies House). It will never be supplied to anyone outside Addstone (UK) Limited without prior authorisation from yourself, unless we are obliged by law to do so. However, if you post or send offensive material on or to Addstone™ or seek to cause damage to our systems, we reserve the right to use whatever information is available to us to stop such activities. We will retain your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the services provided by the Addstone™ website. We will ensure that all personal information supplied will be held securely in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. You agree that you do no				t object to us contacting you for the purposes of processing orders and notification of products or special offers that may be of interest to you, whether by telephone, e-mail or in writing. Furthermore, you confirm that you do not and will not consider any of the above as being a breach of any of your rights under the Telecommunications (Data Protection and Privacy) Regulations 1999.
Right of Access
You have the right to a copy of your personal information held by Addstone™ and have the right to have inaccuracies corrected. (To cover our administrative costs we must charge £25 for such information requests). Please forward requests to Data Protection Department, Addstone (UK) Limited, 4 Westover Drive, Stone, Staffordshire, United Kingdom. ST15 8TT.
Consent
Users aged 16 or below are not allowed to provide us with personal information without parent and/or guardian consent. In such cases please obtain your parents' or guardian's consent prior to providing your personal information to the Addstone™ website.
Cookies
The Addstone™ website may make use of Cookie technology to facilitate operation of the online store and forum / discussion groups.
Questions regarding this Policy should be directed to the Administrative Head Office of Addstone (UK) Limited as follows:Customer Services Manager, Addstone™, 4 Westover Drive, Stone, Staffordshire, United Kingdom. ST15 8TT.
Popular Stock Products:
Addstone™ © 2004-2020; all rights reserved.
